Hello everyone and welcome to a new video here on my channel. Don't worry I'm going to change
back to black for the outfits I'm going to show you. I just thought to give you a little shock
or rather no I just ordered this outfit and wanted to see how it looks especially together
with my hair so I'm just using this for the introduction outfit because today I'm going
to show you a lot of corsets again a Corsostory mini haul I think three
corsets and they're rather black and the outfits going to be black so this is the
colorful part but anyway I'm going to change into the first corset there are
two over bust and one under bust corset and I think I'll start with an over bust one
Tada! This is the first corset. There is a shoulder piece, a lacy shoulder piece, that
is of course optional. I'm going to take it off in a second. But I like the look with
the pearl chains here and overall the color combination. So it's not only black and I
This thing is one of the few overbust corsets I own nowadays.
There's going to be a second one later.
But I like it.
I think it makes a great figure and it looks even better, at least in my opinion, if I'm
going to detach this collar here.
I mean of course you can combine this collar with any other top, so it's quite handy.
this is the look without the collar and yeah as I already said I like it better
this way
oh yeah I combined it with my Fernando Bellin boots and some leggings and I think it's a cool look overall
and there's only a handbag missing and then I could go out. I quickly changed into the second
corset. It's the underboss one and I love this design. I think it looks like a cross somehow
and the little flowers here and kind of like I mean I'm not a fan of flowers but I think it
works with this design because it's also really really nice to lace so there's really
the waist showing off here with this I don't know if it's the design or the cut but I think
this fits just really good so of course the story has a massive range of design and products I have
no idea if these three are still available because I got them like a while ago but I'll try to link
them down below and if I don't find them anymore have a look at the corset story
website because they have a ton of cool designs and always new designs to
explore. There is as with the first corset a top part. I'm not wearing it yet because
this is a cool combination. I love this combination with a top and a corset.
But there is a shrug that comes with the corset with matching design and lace
arms yes anyway I already know that it is a bit too tight for me and I'm such a
short but I'm going to show to you because I think it's a super cute set
together and if you like a bit yeah smaller than me it's going to look
really good
Now I have to go to the mirror and close this.
Okay here we are.
As I already said it's a bit too tight here for me under the arms and a bit too short
and I'm not the biggest fan of high collars for myself.
So yeah this is just to give you an impression about the set.
I think I'm going to not wear this together but only the under bust part because I really like this one.
And this is my kind of shrug. It's a short leather jacket and I think it looks really great together.
I'll see if I can lose it.
Looks good as well.
Yeah, definitely.
I think with this kind of leather jacket I would wear different shoes, maybe my other
Fernandos because they have buckles here at the end, which works together with the jacket.
But yeah, this is how I think I would style this corset.
So what do you prefer, with or without jacket?
I don't know, leave a comment.
Here we go with the third outfit. Again an overbust corset with straps here.
Of course this is totally my color combination with the black and the silver.
And I think it looks really elegant with the straps here.
Also the metal parts and the nice cleavage here.
So it could also work with a long skirt for example maybe?
I don't know.
I'm just doing everything with leggings here today.
Although I have to say that the first one was a bit more comfortable and somehow did fit better.
I don't know.
It's just a feeling.
Oh I like that the back side is different.
The design than the front.
Again, all of the three have cool designs.
I totally love that there is a bit variation going on and it's not only one plain color.
As always with corsets, I recommend to get into your shoes first because it's not really
handy.
So just a tip I always like to remind myself because I'm always like, oh yeah, I want to
wear a corset.
cross them they're like ah damn I have to put on shoes as well yeah but that was everything I
wanted to show you today I hope you had fun with this video have a look in the description text for
any information also I'll link my patreon in the description text so if you want to support me and
this channel have a look there and you'll find my instagram and facebook as well so yeah if you have
any questions write it down in the comments and see you in the next video bye